http://www.greensboro-nc.gov/government/our-website-policy

Show/Hide
Business Owners: Mayor issues emergency declaration reinforcing Governor's Executive Order. effective November 20.
HomeServicesStorm Recovery ResourcesService DirectoryCity Assistance ProgramsClasses/Field Trips for SchoolsEconomic DevelopmentEmergency Notifications – GEANIHomebuyers' Assistance ProgramsHousing Programs and ServicesMedication Collection BoxesParticipatory BudgetingPrograms for SeniorsRegional Transportation PlanningSafe Places in GreensboroSwimming LessonsYellow Dot Program – Emergency Responders AssistanceCity Comes to YouAppliance DisposalBusesBusiness RecyclingDead Animal PickupDumpsterFire InspectionsHousehold Hazardous Waste DisposalLeaf CollectionResidential Recycling CollectionsSecurity Assessment – Home & BusinessSmoke Alarm ReplacementSnow RemovalTrash CollectionWater/Sewer ServiceYard Waste CollectionDiversity and InclusionJobsLive Support ChatLook Up and AccessBid on ContractsCity Building & Facility LocationsCrime MappingCrime ReportsGIS MappingHomes/Property for SaleInteractive Land Development OrdinanceOpen Data PortalWater Bill AccessWifi LocationsWorkforce DevelopmentOnline Payments & ServicesRequestsBuilding Plan Submissions and TrackingBuilding / Development Process: Commercial and ResidentialCity Service RequestsCode Compliance: Personal Property & Housing CodesFair Housing AssistanceOvergrown YardsPermits, Licenses and FeesPublic Improvements RequestPublic Records RequestsRenting a City FacilityStreet Light RequestsZoning/Rezoning
DepartmentsBudget & EvaluationCemeteriesColiseumCommunications & MarketingCommunity RelationsContact CenterCreative GreensboroEngineering & InspectionsExecutiveOffice of Equity and InclusionCommunity Services TeamField OperationsGSO CollectsFinancial & Administrative ServicesFireGuilford Metro 9-1-1Human RightsRACE GSOHuman ResourcesInformation TechnologyLegalLegislativeGreensboro Criminal Justice Advisory CommissionLibraries Neighborhood DevelopmentHousing Connect GSOParks & RecreationPlanningLEED for CitiesGSO2040PoliceRecent Directives UpdatesTransportationGreensboro Transit Agency/Public Transportation DivisionMetropolitan Planning OrganizationParkingWater Resources
GSO Collects App
Never miss your trash or recycling pickup
GovernmentZoom BackgroundsCity Service Request2016 Bond Referendum ApprovedAbout UsOrganizational ChartDemographicsBoards and CommissionsCity ClerkNC Government Records BranchCity CouncilMeeting CalendarMeeting Agendas, Minutes & VideosAgendas for Council Work SessionsCouncil Committees - Prior to September 1, 2015Frequently Asked QuestionsWhat Council District Am I In?Council District MapE-mail City CouncilClosed Session Meeting MinutesCity Manager's OfficeCity News2020 Holiday Calendar2021 Holiday CalendarAt Your Service City CalendarCity Calendar (meetings)City Connections (e-newsletter)City Newse-NotifyOfficial Social Media SitesRoad ClosuresRSS FeedsTelevised MeetingsVideos on DemandCode of OrdinancesCommunity Food Task ForceCurrent BudgetMayor's Committee for Persons with DisabilitiesAccess GreensboroBecoming a MemberMeetingsInformation and ReferralsLibrary ResourcesAwardsPublic Records Requests
What District Am I In?
ResidentsUS Census 2020CommunityActive Adults 50+BeautificationCemeteriesCommunity Food Task ForceFarmers MarketGreensboro Cultural Arts Master Plan (GCAMP)HousingMapsPoolsSports & PlayRentals & EventsVolunteer OpportunitiesWi-FiDiversity and InclusionExploreArts & EventsColiseum ComplexConvention & Visitors BureauGreensboro Cultural CenterGreensboro Farmers Curb MarketDowntown Greensboro Inc. GardensChamber of Commerce Greensboro History MuseumGreensboro Science CenterLibraryParksSports FacilitiesTrailsFacility DirectoryFacility Directory (Map View)Make Online PaymentsOnline FormsProgramsAdopt-A-ParkAdopt-a-StreamCultural Center ClassesParticipatory BudgetingRecycling EducationRegional Transportation PlanningPublic SafetyCommercial Building Safety IssuesCommunity Watch ProgramCrime DataEmergency PreparednessFalse AlarmsGEANI Emergency NotificationsHousing Safety Issues"Safe Places" in GreensboroSmoke Alarm ReplacementText to 911Yellow Dot ProgramView MoreRecyclingRequest a City ServiceTransitBus Schedules, Routes, Stops, etc.Downtown ParkingSCATTrashWater / Sewer Bills
BusinessEconomic Development & Business SupportEconomic Development Focus StrategyOpportunity ZonesAssistance & ProgramsIndustry Recruitment & ExpansionResourcesBidding OpportunitiesDevelopment ServicesContact InformationResidents/HomeownersDesign Professionals & DevelopersContractors - Residential & Commercial Minority and Women's Business EnterpriseMED Week 2020Becoming a Certified FirmFinding Certified FirmsLocal and State Bid OpportunitiesDisparity Study 2018Office of Workforce DevelopmentRoad Project Mapping ToolSpecial Event Permits
I Want To...Apply ForBicycle Registration (online form)Boards & CommissionsJobsLibrary CardPermits & LicensesRequest a Public Record/DocumentBid OnContactContact the CityE-mail City CouncilLive Support ChatDownload AppsExplore GreensboroGet Around The CityBus RoutesPublic Parking/GTA (List View)Learn AboutActive Adult ProgramsActivitiesArts & EntertainmentBeautification EffortsCity EventsCity NewsCode Violations & CompliancesDiversity & InclusionEmergency PreparationsRecycling Safety IssuesWeather-Related Closings/Schedule ChangesCovid-19 Information and UpdatesLocateBidding OpportunitiesCity HallCity Buildings & FacilitiesRoad ProjectsSafe PlacesWiFi LocationsPay ForReportAccidentsComplaints/Commendations (police)CrimeOrdinance ViolationsPotholesStreet Light, Signal, Sign Problem / IssueWater in the StreetWater PollutionWebsite IssuesSign Up ForCommercial Dumpster Servicee-Billing (Water / Sewer) e-NotifyLibrary CardParks and Recreation Programs/ServicesPark Shelter ReservationsScheduling Inspections (building, permit)Speaking at City Council Meetings / Submitting Comments Before MeetingsWater ServiceWatchGreensboro Television Network (GTN) LiveCity Council Meetings OnlineVideos on DemandZoning Commission Meetings OnlineSite Map
View/download the pdf version of the privacy policy.
Purpose
This policy describes privacy practices regarding information collected from the City of Greensboro website. It contains information about what data is collected and how that information is used. This policy may be updated periodically, so please check back from time to time.
This policy applies only to the official City of Greensboro website (www.greensboro-nc.gov). When you follow a link to another website, even the site of another governmental agency, you are subject to the privacy policy of that site. You should check the privacy policies of each of these other sites if you have questions about how they handle personally identifiable information.
Automatic Collection of Certain Information
No personally identifiable information is collected from visitors who simply browse this site or who download information from it. While our Web servers maintain logs of user activity to help us manage the website, information stored in these logs or in cookies does not identify you personally. The logs store things such as the domain name and IP address from which you accessed our site, the pages visited, and the address of the site that you linked to us from (if you linked to our website from another website).
We use this information to learn how many visitors we have, where they are coming from, which parts of our website are of most interest to visitors, and other facts that will help us improve the website and the services we offer.
If You Send Us Personal Information
Visitors who request services through this site may be required to furnish additional information in order for us to provide the service requested. The additional information collected will be no more specific than if the visitor were requesting the service by any other means, including by telephone or an in-person visit to a City facility. If you participate in a survey, send us an e-mail, or submit an online form, your e-mail address and the other information you volunteered will be collected. We may share this information with other governmental agencies or organizations to provide the help you are requesting. We may also use that information to help assess user needs and analyze trends.
If you use this website for electronic commerce, we may collect, process, and disclose your name, address and payment information (if applicable) to the extent necessary to complete the online transaction and for record-keeping activities such as billing, permits and licenses.
Certain types of personal information constitute public records, which means that we must provide it to persons making public records requests. However, this does not include the account numbers you use for electronic payment, public enterprise billing information and certain other types of protected information.
Security
Some information that you submit to us through this website may be protected by encryption technology, whereas other information may not. Unless a particular Web page on this site indicates that encryption technology is being used, you should not assume that information you submit through that Web page will be secure. If you submit information to our server through a Web page containing visible indicators of active encryption technology, we will take reasonable precautions to safeguard the confidentiality of such information. However, no website can protect itself against all eventualities. The City of Greensboro will not be held liable for any injury caused by the disclosure of your information, whether by security breach, accident, inadvertence, or any other act resulting in disclosure.
Use of Cookies
Cookies or other technology may transfer information from this website to your hard disk for record-keeping purposes. Cookies or similar technology can make the Internet more useful by storing information about your preferences on a particular site. The use of cookies or similar technology is an industry standard, and this website, like many others, uses them to provide useful features for our users. Cookies in and of themselves do not personally identify you, although they do identify your computer. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. If you prefer, you can set your browser to refuse cookies. However, you may not be able to take full advantage of this website if you do so.
Public Records
Read how to submit a request for a public record or document. The City of Greensboro is governed by North Carolina Public Records Laws. This means that the information we receive online may be disclosed to any person making a public records request, unless the record is exempted from disclosure. Only very narrowly defined types of information (such as electronic payment information and Social Security numbers) are exempt from disclosure as public records. If you have questions about the North Carolina Public Records Law, refer to NC General Statute Chapter 132. For purposes of determining whether information is a public record, information sent to us through this website is treated the same as information sent to us by mail or delivered to us in person.
Children
No applications on this website specifically solicit information from minors or seek to determine whether the visitor is a minor. Consequently, visitors should be aware that the collection of personal information requested from or volunteered by children online or by e-mail will be treated in the same manner as information given by an adult. Among other things, this means that it will be public record and therefore will be subject to public access. We ask that parents guide their children when children are asked to provide personal information online. We ask that children get their parents’ permission before providing any information to us.
Privacy of E-mail Lists
The City of Greensboro maintains e-mail lists, but only of those individuals or organizations that have specifically opted to receive updates and other information from the City. These lists include members of the media and interested members of the general public who have specifically requested to be kept informed about City affairs. Under current North Carolina law, these e-mail lists are public records and we must provide them to anyone who makes a public records request, except to the extent that they contain public enterprise billing information or other information protected from disclosure by law.
Unless you request that we delete any of the information you submitted when you registered for any electronic updates and/or newsletters we may offer, we may store such information indefinitely.
View Full Site
